(Penny:)A prenup?
Heh, wow.
(Leonard:)What are you gonna do?
(Bernadette:)I don't know.
(Raj:)Follow your heart.
You know what?
It's not a big deal.
I mean,
she makes more money than me.
(Howard:)She wants to protect
her financial interests.
(Howard:)- It's completely reasonable.
- Good, that's a heaIthy attitude.
(Howard:)Actually, it's good for both of us.
I have assets to protect too.
(Raj:)Like what?
Well, I've got some rare comic books.
(Penny:)You know,
the Vespa's almost paid off.
(Howard:)Ma and I have a primo
double cemetery plot at Mt. Sinai...
(Howard:)...right near the guy who played
Mr. Roper on Three's Company.
(Raj:)Mr. Roper's dead?
(Raj:)You can't just spring that on a guy.